[
    {
        "front": "かいがい",
        "back": "overseas",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅっちょう（する）",
        "back": "to go on a business trip",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょくせつ",
        "back": "directly",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "もどる",
        "back": "to return",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいぎ",
        "back": "conference",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひま",
        "back": "(free) time",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たおれる",
        "back": "to fall (ill)",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうそう（する）",
        "back": "competion / to  compete",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "かつ",
        "back": "to beat; to win",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "まける",
        "back": "to lose",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "しかたが ない",
        "back": "cannot be helped",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "にゅういん（する）",
        "back": "hospitalization /  to be hospitalized",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "なおる",
        "back": "to recover",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいいん（する）",
        "back": "to be discharged",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    },
    {
        "front": "きをつける",
        "back": "to be careful",
        "chapter": "N4 C16"
    }
]